ikonfx.com 2010-12-10

# Ikon Group Privacy Statement - Ikon Group

  * Home
  * About Us
    * Ikon Group Introduction
    * Regulatory Status
    * IKON Milestone
    * Senator Larry Pressler
    * Our Offices
    * Brochure Download
  * Our Advantage
    * Our Advantage
    * API System
  * Products
    * Ikon MT4 Matrix
    * Ikon Currenex Viking
    * Ikon Mega Institutional
    * Ikon Turbo Meta
    * Ikon Mega
    * Futures-Ikon Elite
    * Option-Ikon Prime
    * CFDs-Ikon Supreme
    * NASDAQ-Ikon NFX Futures Platform
    * NDF-Ikon Mega
  * Brokers and Partners
    * Introducing Broker
    * White Label
    * Senior Partners
    * Request a Video Conference
  * Accounts
    * Live account
    * Demo account
  * Client Information
    * Deposit Fund
    * File Download
    * Forex FAQs
    * Ikon FAQs
    * Trading FAQs
    * Emergency Telephone Orders
    * Economic Calendar
    * Official Statement
  * Contact Us
  * Contest
    * Register
    * Ranking

## Ikon Group Privacy Statement

## Contact Us

001-6465581399  
001-212-796-6899

## Ikon Group Privacy Statement

Ikon Group, Ikon Global Markets Inc, Ikon Capital Limited, IFSCL NZ (Ikon FX NZ) or any other trading Company under the Brand name of Ikon (collectively referred to hereinafter as  “Ikon Group Affiliated Companies”) are committed to safeguarding  the personal information that you provide us. Ikon Group Affiliated Companies do not disclose any nonpublic information about our customers to anyone except as permitted by law. 

Personal Information We Collect 

When you apply for or maintain an account with Ikon Group Affiliated Companies they collect personal information about you for business purposes, such as evaluating your financial needs, processing your requests and transactions, informing you about products and services that may be of interest to you and providing customer service. The personal information we collect about you includes: 

Information you provide to us on application and other forms, such as your name, address, and date of birth, social security number, occupation, assets and income.   
Information about your transactions with us and with our affiliates.   
Information we receive from consumer reporting agencies.   
Information you provide to us to verify your identity, such as a passport, or driver’s license, etc. 

Confidentiality and Security 

We limit access to your personal information to those employees who need to know in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain your account documentation with personal information in physically locked file cabinets.  Electronic access to personal information in the system is also limited to New Accounts and Credit personnel.  These procedural safeguards are designed to protect your nonpublic information. We do not rent or sell your name or personal information to anyone. 

Disclosure to Non-Affiliated Third  Parties 

In order to support the  financial products and services we provide to you, Ikon Group Affiliated Companies  may share the personal information described above with  third-party service providers and joint marketers not  affiliated with us, including: Companies under contract  to perform services for us or on our behalf, such as  vendors that prepare and mail statements and  transactions confirmations or provide data processing,  computer software maintenance and development,  transaction processing and marketing services. These companies acting on our behalf are required to keep your personal information confidential. 

Also, we may disclose personal information to regulatory authorities as permitted or required by applicable law. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property.
